http://www.flyariana.com/Corp/privacy

Privacy Policy
Ariana is concerned about your right to privacy. When you visit the Ariana web sites, you can be assured that any information you share with us will be treated with the utmost confidentiality and will not be disclosed to any entity outside of Ariana or its Partners.
Ariana does not sell personal information about individual members (such as name, address, Email address) to third parties. We do not sell or rent lists of members or use information about individual members outside the scope of the Ariana umbrella of services. Ariana reserves the right to disclose aggregated information regarding its members and usage of the Ariana umbrella of services (such as member demographics and traffic patterns) to advertisers, partners and others for various purposes.
IP Address
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site under the Terms and Conditions of the Service Agreement. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information.
Financial Information
Credit card information may be collected each time an order is placed for Ariana travel. The information collected will include, but not be limited to name, billing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This information will be retained on the site in the secure environment covered under "Secure", and processed by a third party.
Your information is only accessible to you through use of your NIC# and secret password. We do not store your credit card information, only your name, address, password, travel history, AirMiles™ history, telephone number and email.
Disclosing Information
www.flyariana.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others without your prior consent. We may share non-personal, aggregate statistical information regarding our customers, sales, traffic patterns and site usage with our partners. For example, we may develop aggregated summary, not individual, reports for our partners and affiliates. At no time will we separate out individuals or tell partners individual information without your consent. Ariana reserves the right to disclose any personal information to any third party in order to operate the site for compliance with legal obligations, governmental requests, or our code of conduct.
Links to other Sites
This site may contain links to other sites. Ariana is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Updating Account Information
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided by visiting www.flyariana.com. You may update your personal information, opt in/out of email updates and manage your Ariana Loyalty Club account.
Your Consent
By using the www.flyariana.com site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Ariana. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. www.flyariana.com reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update these policies, and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations, or updates.
Contacting www.flyariana.com about this site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Ariana at: +93-75-2040913
About Us
History
Mission Statement
Fleet Information
Flight Schedule
Site Map
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
©Ariana Afghan Airlines 2020. Powered by Zapways Inc.
